BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6)
1948- 1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/006
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
Contracts are arranged alphabetically by trade name. The original collection number for this series was 66A-1307.
5833598
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Collective labor agreements -- United States; United States. Department of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics
5833598
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Asbestos Workers, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Boilermakers, 1948-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bookbinders (B&J), 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bricklayers, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bricklayers' Tenders, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Building Laborers, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Carpenters, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cement Masons, 1948-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Compositors (B&J), 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Compositors (B&J), 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Compositors (Newspaper), 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Electricians (Inside Wiremen), 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Electrotypers and Stereotypers (B&J), 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Elevator Constructors, 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Engineers, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Glaziers, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Lathers, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local Transit, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Machinists, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Mailers (B&J), 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Mailers (Newspaper), 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Marble Setters, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Marble Setters' Helpers, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Painters, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Paperhangers, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Photoengravers (B&J), 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Photoengravers (B&J), 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Photoengravers (Newspaper), 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pipefitters, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Plasterers, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Plasterers' Laborers, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Plumbers, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Plumbers' Laborers, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Pressmen (B&J), 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Pressmen (Newspaper), 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Rodmen, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Roofers (Slate and Tile), 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sheet-Metal Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Stereotypers (Newspaper), 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Stonemasons, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Structural Iron Workers, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Terrazzo Workers' Helpers, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Tile Layers, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Tile Layers' Helpers, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Albuquerque, NM, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Atlanta, GA, 1961-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Baltimore, MD, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Birmingham, AL, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Boston, MA, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Buffalo, NY, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Charlotte, NC, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Chicago, IL, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Cincinnati, OH, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Cleveland, OH, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Columbus, OH, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Dallas, TX, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Denver, CO, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Des Moines, IO, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Detroit, MI, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Evansville, IN, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Fresno, CA, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Grand Rapids, MI, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Houston, TX, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Jacksonville, FL., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Kansas City, MO, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Knoxville, TN, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Little Rock, AR, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, CA, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Louisville, KY, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Madison, WI, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Memphis, TN, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee, WI, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Minneapolis-St. Paul, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- New Orleans, LA, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- New York, NY, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Newark, NJ, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Norfolk, VA, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Oklahoma City, OK, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Omaha, NE, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Peoria, IL, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Pittsburg, PA, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Philadelphia, PA, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Phoenix, AZ, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Portland, OR, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Richmond, VA, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Sacramento, CA, 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- St. Louis, MO, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Salt Lake City, UT, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- San Diego, CA, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- San Francisco, CA, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Seattle, WA, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- South Bend, IA, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Spokane, WA, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Springfield, MA, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Tampa, FL, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Toledo, OH, 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Tulsa, OK, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Public Housing Receipts, Various Cities, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)